what up I know you like to be held the
other way but you know um so guess what
we're doing right now thank you you're
welcome you're welcome
guess we're doing right now well I'm
eating a sandwich hmm
eating sculpey but yeah we have a patch
that maybe will enable stop and go on
our rav4 wouldn't that be nice
mmm that IO like says everything that
our Lex has a torque mod the isle X has
a official Tama built , pedal I didn't
make the model bus our head of machine
learning and our head of localization
did I'm the social media guy I also
occasionally brick cars we're gonna find
out right now are uning
ants on a log no I mean your sandwich
bro want some sandwich Kobe's no Sam I'm
all guys not a myth and localization
that guy did get a race um como space
forest well you know I think aliens are
one of the biggest threats to human
society and we need to mobilize our
governments resources to put military
bases on the Moon and Mars and Venus
even mercury no more no more
military bases and in Iraq and Russia
and only only space I'm a fem
I'm sure give me a job to comment I
didn't say you're hired you do print 3d
printing things for us a new complicated
lock on our door
cool time now
freestyle Tuesday go to Berkeley tonight
guys taking the a chord all right
so you see this rap for
this is the rav4s final resting place
because we're about to brick it split
around there looks go bezel splitter
right here apart oh hey guys if we drove
a long us bead we won't find one of
those two laptop right here is that an
extension once an exception pandas are
super reliable so that's why they work
with extension cakes so we're now using
a panda to flash by choosing attack
tricks to flash and we're using the
official Toyota calibration update
wizard software wizard Wow okay all
rights go peace was that a little dizzy
so I'm sitting here on my macbook pro
here's our here's our patching software
here's the Toyota stuff loaded up in Ida
oh yeah this is from when we had Tripoli
on tech no Dooley on tech is
discontinued
well this PC @mods work on all Toyota
hopefully so my job
Ricardo's job is to run the flash my job
is to sit here and run the sniff all
right oh I'm not connected to a panda
sorry I put you down wait no was off
well sorry for putting you down scope
ease let's see if we no connection turn
the switch off oh well now it probably
went into CDP mode so just
power cycle data yeah okay cool just
make sure I stay connected all right we
are connected to panda I don't know I
just lost connection is the Porsche yeah
yeah left a single part of the pan well
but okay okay something's wrong turn
power off and the pompously no and panda
loses power
how does it make sense powered by the
RAF
[Music]
turn that off and it loses power yes
what does make any sense at all write
letter broken that'd be weird you guys
make sure to buy this buy quality comma
we test your pant is better than we test
ours it works now so splitter sucks that
doesn't make sense
she's like Sheldon good no we don't saw
the comma splitter that's the problem
this is off Amazon can I take your gray
pan to bag why is it broken
did you break it chase now if you broke
it I don't want a diagonal broken panda
I'm just like you would you want a
broken Panda do you want off oh now it's
working cool oh good alright so this is
a really low-quality periscope Kris you
should have got very bad here the camera
person no messages turn the car on ah
not really messages accessories fine
right yeah accessories fine if the
default if the reason your panda broke
was our fault we'll send you a new panda
if you did something stupid shout that
comma da di bro alright so here we are
in the Toyota calibration update wizard
yeah running a special patched version
downloading karma combination so I've
hacked this cue file to reflash over
already-existing
cuz it's not actually
[Music]
alright we're downloading currently
chase yes I yes I know I know okay he
did something stupid to break his pen I
know alright so this is the current
calibration ID it was actually a real
update for the rav4 too and this is the
new calibration ID model named rav4 okay
so it looks good
there's now no way back now watch you
have the vehicle one which has to go
back but what I'm gonna do it oh it's
being censored by potato res no wait is
the resolution bad some guys suggested
some app oh I'm sorry scope ease why are
they so low quality can somebody fix
periscope yeah we're good we're good
it's just Kim oh well now you turn off
doesn't matter yeah you see a black
circle it's great okay wait is there any
way to fix this okay another man hang on
hang on hang in hand
I okay is that better
oh yeah you're bored anyway bye yeah but
I thought you got Wi-Fi out here is that
worse it's worse
okay well it's a low quality Prius bring
sck oh no the scope is are disappeared
George you look like a Lego let's drag
it into why my bitrate
how often if I can broadcast details
oh is it better
oh it's better oh good good good is it
good or just like mildly better good
enough let's know where the battery dies
cool turning vision on a sniffers
restarted I don't think we can actually
have this car started I think you have
to get one of the things flash
calibration update and progress to the
service last night or not no we never
went to this point oh oh good I saw the
country on the flashing cool we're
flashing oh yeah don't touch anything
Daivari scobie's were staying very still
right now I know you have a little
quality flash calibration update in
progress I see a Toyota black line all
right we're gonna seriously look into
periscope quality we're gonna hire a
periscope this is good okay do you guys
see flash calibration update oh I moved
no no
if we stay very still yeah kids wolf no
stupid
Tommy's fake yeah the time it's fake
good this is this is the stuff flowing
through the canvas it's flowing chase
wants to be periscope follow me man yeah
I see a blue line in a white truck I
mean yeah that's basically what there is
to see right now no no no no we're gonna
get better periscopes we need an outdoor
access play baby
they only see the matron I see the
things scrolling by yeah I've missed New
Jersey to file all right there
yeah I think everything to try then we
can try with the joystick cool actually
no yeah then there's some chance we just
like broke please control entirely yeah
Wow we're literally just live-streaming
a progress bar going up yes yeah it's
almost done flashing yeah yeah we're
breaking the onboard firmware you guys
will get to go through this lovely
process if you won't stop and go and
your cars to actually we will probably
write a panda base flasher we're not
gonna recommend our competitor oh look
at all the malfunctions huh well that
one's normal that one's normal yeah oh
okay been loaded successfully we're
ignition off very careful then next
please wait ten seconds the battery is
too low yeah you want stop and go in
your Honda you know what you need
[Music]
alright well this is where we know if it
bricked really successful despite that
terrible red stuff that's what's good
yeah onto puddle all right so let me
just commit that flash log should've
called it rav4 PC every flash is dumb
yeah okay so none of these are safe free
flashes they're PCM so let's start the
car and see what works yeah like if the
cab rides well yeah I guess yeah well
let's see if yeah the engine still works
no EPS flash no no ups flashes band okay
okay so let's try it with the joystick
no it was a live flashing guys and that
was all fingers things gonna work I
don't know my skull piece you got to see
the cool part it didn't break psyche it
was clipping